The Carleton Hodge collection: books from the library of Carleton Hodge Z7770 .H6
Lilly Library
- O (Box 48)
  - Old testament pseudepigrapha. Edited by James H. Charlesworth. New York, London, Toronto, Sydney and Auckland: Doubleday, 1983-1985 (Box 46)
    - Vol. 1 Apocalyptic literature and testaments, 1983 (Box 46)
    - Vol. 2 Expansions of the "Old testament" and legends, wisdom and philosophical literature, ..., 1985 (Box 46)
  - Olson, Genevieve P. Life of Christ Jesus in bible language from the King James version of the bible. Fifth edition, revised Wheaton edition. Bonita, CA: Genevieve Olson, 1966 (Box 56)
  - Osgoodby, William W. Matchless life the records of the four evangelists arranged in a continuous narrative. Rochester, N.Y.: Life Publishing Company, 1913 (Box 55)
  - Oursler, Fulton. Greatest book ever written the old testament story. Garden City, NY: Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1951 (Box 39)
- P (Box 39)
  - Pamplona bibles by François Bucher a facsimile compiled from two picture bibles with martyrologies commissioned by King Sancho el Fuerte of Navarra ... New Haven and London: Yale University Press, 1970 (Box 48)
    - Vol.1 Text (Box 48)
    - Vol.2 facsimile (Box 48)
  - Pandzhabsko-russkiĭ solvar'. Sostavili I.S. Rabinovich I I. D. Serebriakov. Okolo 35 000 solv. ... Moskva: Gos. Izd-vo inostrannykh I natsional'nykh solvareĭ, 1961 (Box 38)
  - Papyrus Bodmer II Evangile de Jean chap 1-14. Cologny-Genéve: Bibliothéque Bodmer, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Papyrus Bodmer XIV-XV Evangiles de Luc et Jean Tome I XIV: Luc chap. 3-34. Cologny-Genéve: Bibliothéque Bodmer(In box w/ Tome II), 1961 (Box 31)
  - Papyrus Bodmer XIV-XV Evangiles de Luc et Jean Tome II XV: Jean chap. 1-15. Cologny-Genéve: Bibliothéque Bodmer(In box w/ Tome I), 1961 (Box 31)
  - Papyrus Bodmer II Supplément Evangile de Jean chap14-21 Nouvelle édition agumentée et corrigée ... Cologny-Genéve: Bibliothéque Bodmer, 1962 (Box 31)
  - Paul's letters to the Corinthians -- The twentieth century translation. Lincoln, NE: Back to the Bible Publishers, 1961 (Box 56)
  - Pietersma, Albert. Chester Beatty biblical papyri IV and V a new edition with text-critical analysis. Toronto: Samuel Stevens Hakkert and companyAmerican studies in papyrology volume sixteen., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Posner, Raphael and Israel Ta-Shema eds. Hebrew book an historical survey. New York: Leon Amiel Publisher, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Psaumes de David. Proverbes de Salomon. Ecclésiaste. A Toulouse: De l'Imprimerie d'Antoine Navarre, 1819 (Box 55)
- Q (Box 55)
- R (Box 55)
  - Readings from the holy scriptures prepared for the use of Jewish personnel of the army of the United States Published under the direction of the chief of chaplins. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1942 (Box 56)
  - Robertson, A.T. Harmony of the gospels for students of the life of Christ based on the Bradus Harmony in the revised version. New York, Evanston and London: Harper & Row, 1950 (Box 46)
  - Robertson, Edward. Harmony of the four gospels in English. According to the common version. Newly arranged, with explanatory notes. Tenth edition. Boston: Crocker & Brewster and London: Wiley & Putnam, 1862 (Box 46)
  - Romer, John. Testament the Bible and history. New York: Henry Holt and Company, 1988 (Box 27)
- S (Box 27)
  - Sanders, Henry A. and Carl Schmidt. Minor prophets in the Freer Collection and the Berlin Fragment of Genesis. New York: Macmillan Company and London: Macmillan and Company, 1927 (Box 30)
  - Schouppe, F.X. Explanatio Psalmorum qui juxta breviarium romanum in officiis communibus recitantur, ad mentem optimorum interpretum adornata. Bruxellis: Ex Officinia Catholica M.Closson et Sociorum and Buscoduci: Apud W. Van Gulick and Parisiis: Apud Bray et Retaux, [1880?] (Box 56)
  - Serendipity New Testament for groups Second edition New international version. Littleton, CO: Serendipity HousePreview Sample: Gospel of Matthew & Mark., 1987 (Box 55)
  - Sermon on the mount. New York: Chicago: Los Angeles: American Bible Society, [ca. 1960] (Box 56)
  - Sermon on the mount being the fifth, sixth & seventh chapters of the gospel according to St. Matthew in the King James version of the holy bible. Chicago: Monastery Hill Bindery, 1968 (Box 55)
  - Smith, Wade C. Little Jetts Bible. Boston: W.A. Wilde Company, 1942 (Box 20)
  - Steinmueller, John E. Gospel harmony using the confraternity edition of the new testament. New York and Chicago: W.H. Sadlier Inc., 1942 (Box 55)
  - Stevens, Wm. Arnold and Ernest Dewitt Burton. Harmony of the Gospels for historical study an analytical synopsis of the four Gospels in the version of 1881. New York: International committee of Young Men's Christian Associations, 1903 (Box 8)
  - Stevens, Wm. Arnold and Ernest Dewitt Burton. Harmony of the Gospels for historical study an analytical synopsis of the four Gospels. Tenth edition, revised. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1911 (Box 8)
- T (Box 8)
  - Treasures from the bible. New York: Essential Books, 1944 (Box 46)
- U (Box 46)
- V (Box 46)
  - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem. Story of the bible. New York: Boni & Liveright, 1923 (Box 55)
- W (Box 55)
  - Walks and words of Jesus a paragraph harmony of the four gospels originally compiled by Rev. M.N. Olmsted to which is added "New saying of Jesus" revised edition. New York: Oxford University Press, 1918 (Box 37)
  - Watkins, I.B. Scripture history; containing all the important passags in the Old and New Testaments. Designed for the improvement of youth, and as a useful introduction to the knowledge of the sacred scriptures. In twenty five numbers, embellished with 200 engravings. ... New York: Printed and published by Thomas Kinnersley, 1829 (Box 38)
    - Vol. 1 (Box 38)
    - Vol. 2 (Box 38)
  - Watts, Isaac. Psalms of David, imitated in the language of the New Testament, and applied to the Christian state and worship. Walpole, N.H.: Isaiah Thomas & Co., 1812 (Box 22)
  - Wilkins, Chester. Four Gospels arranged as a single narrative. Berne, Ind.: Light & Hope Publishing, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Wisdom for modern man Proverbs and Ecclesiastes from the old testament in today's English version. New York: American Bible Society, 1972 (Box 56)
  - Words of Jesus as recorded in the authorized King James version of the Holy Bible comprising the words of Jesus with authoritative adaptations of the Bible text of which the are a part arranged and chronicled by Gilbert James Brett ... Chicago: Consolidated Book Publishers, 1965 (Box 37)
- X (Box 37)
- Y (Box 37)
  - Young, Robert. Young's literal translation of the Holy Bible. Revised edition. Grand Rapids, MI: Baker Book House, [1976-1977?] (Box 22)
- Z (Box 22)